<user><name> Abdullah Baaj </name><title> Adjunct Lecturer </title><department> Departments/Programs The Heller School for Social Policy and Management </department><degrees> Degrees Northeastern University, Pharm.D. Tufts University, M.D. </degrees><expertise></expertise><profile></profile><courses> Courses Taught   HS  343f Health Care Entrepreneurship   </courses><awards></awards><scholarship></scholarship><contact> </contact></user><user><name> Bernard Yack </name><title> Lerman Neubauer Professor of Democracy and Public Policy </title><department> Departments/Programs German, Russian, and Asian Languages and Literature Politics </department><degrees> Degrees Harvard University, Ph.D. University of Toronto, B.A. </degrees><expertise> Expertise Political theory. History of political thought. Nationalism. Cultural pluralism. Democratic Theory </expertise><profile> Expertise Political theory. History of political thought. Nationalism. Cultural pluralism. Democratic Theory </profile><courses> Courses Taught   POL  10a Introduction to Political Theory   POL  186b Classical Political Thought   POL  187b Conservative Political Thought   POL  189a Marx, Nietzsche, and Twentieth-Century Radicalism   POL  192b Seminar: Topics in Law and Political Theory   POL  211a Graduate Seminar: Political Theory   POL  340d Proseminar   </courses><awards></awards><scholarship> Scholarship Yack, Bernard. "Loyalty versus Fidelity: A Study in Moral Pluralism." Social Research (2020). (forthcoming) Yack, Bernard. "Of Scribes and Tribes: Enlightenment, Democracy and Populist Revolt." Critical Review (2020). (forthcoming) Yack, Bernard. ""Shklar's Montaigne: A Genealogy of Liberal Morals"." Judith Shklar Reconsidered. Ed. Samantha Ashenden and Andreas Hess. Penn State Press, 2019 (forthcoming) Yack, Bernard. ""Political Liberalism, Political not Philosophical." Perspectives on Political Science 15. (2017): 146-51. Yack, Bernard. ""Democracy and the Love of Truth"." Truth and Democracy. Ed. Jeremy Elkins and Andrew Norris. Philadelphia: University of Pennsylvania Press, 2012. 165-80. Yack, Bernard. Nationalism and the Moral Psychology of Community. Chicago: University of Chicago Press, 2012. Yack, Bernard. ""Rhetoric and Public Reason: An Aristotelian Theory of Deliberation." Political Theory 34. (2006): 417-38. Yack, Bernard. The Fetishism of Modernities: Epochal Self-Consciousness in Contemporary Social and Political Thought. University of Notre Dame Press, 1997. Yack, Bernard. Liberalism without Illusions: Essays on Liberal Theory and the Political Vision of Judith N. Shklar. University of California Press, 1996. Yack, Bernard. The Problems of a Political Animal: Community, Conflict, and Justice in Aristotelian Political Thought. University of California Press, 1993. Yack, Bernard. The Longing for Total Revolution: Philosophic Sources of Social Discontent from Rousseau to Marx and Nietzsche. Princeton University Press, 1986. </scholarship><contact> yack@brandeis.edu 781-736-2640  Olin-Sang American Civilization Center, 107 </contact></user><user><name> Jacob Burg </name><title> Lecturer in University Writing </title><department> Departments/Programs Writing Program </department><degrees> </degrees><expertise></expertise><profile></profile><courses> Courses Taught   UWS  5a When Fantasy Meets Reality   UWS  27a The Western: Cowpunchers, Gunslingers, and Beyond   UWS  30b 140 Characters or Less: Social Media and Public Conversation   </courses><awards></awards><scholarship></scholarship><contact> burgja@brandeis.edu </contact></user>